## PETER KRYSINSKI

SOFTWARE ENGINEER

#### **DETAILS**

#### **ADDRESS**

381 J. St. Salt Lake City, 84103 United States

#### PHONE

313.300.8118

#### **EMAIL**

pakrysin@gmail.com

#### LINKS

<u>Portfolio</u>

<u>GitHub</u>

**LinkedIn** 

#### SKILLS

React.js

Node.js

Express.js

HTML & CSS

JavaScript

MongoDB

SQL

MySQL

NoSQL

GraphQL

Bootstrap

Material UI

Bulma UI

MVC

Git

#### PROFILE

Full-stack web developer with a background in software engineering in various industries including enterprise level healthcare applications and automotive automation systems. Recently trained at the University of Utah coding bootcamp and earned a certificate in full-stack web development. Proven and demonstrable experience combining people skills with technical ability while building fast, efficient, and complex applications from conception to production with modern tech. Also loves all kinds of outdoor recreation, activities with friends, and eating his way around town.

#### **EMPLOYMENT HISTORY**

## Sr. Software Engineer, Centene Corporation

Salt Lake City

Jul 2014 — Present

Started as a junior developer working with the communications department helping program healthcare campaign software processes and patient EOB's. Was promoted to mid-level developer and advanced to the claims adjudication and payments team. Helped develop and improve numerous aspects of the claims processing tool, including 3rd party software integration with SFTP systems and API's. Now a senior engineer, helping build modernization platforms with modern tech to help convert legacy systems to modern architecture.

## Controls Engineer, The Paslin Co.

Detroit

Mar 2013 — Jul 2014

PLC programming and controls design for automated welding systems, HMI/Panel View configuration, troubleshooting and debugging of automation hardware and software. Customer-focused and teamwork driven projects for clients including Honda and Ford. International and domestic travel, up to 80%.

## EDUCATION

## **Certificate, University of Utah**

Salt Lake City, UT

Syracuse, NY

Oct 2022 — Apr 2023

Full Stack Web Development Boot Camp

# Bachelor of Science, Information Management & Technology, Syracuse University

Sep 2008 — Dec 2012